thewebshowroom.com.au 2016-05-10

# Web Design and Search Engine Optimisation Privacy

The Web Showroom, as a leader in [web design](http://www.thewebshowroom.com.au/), is committed to protecting your privacy. We understand that visitors and users of this website are concerned about their privacy and the confidentiality and security of any information that is provided to us. This Privacy Statement details how we generally manage your personal information and safeguard your privacy.

We may collect information about you where it is necessary for us to perform our functions. The information we collect about you depends on how and why you access the website, the information you choose to provide to us, and the types of information and services you request from us.

If you visit our website to browse, read or download information, our system may record anonymous information about the visit such as the number of pages visited and the duration of the visit so we can evaluate site usage to make improvements. Your identity cannot be reasonably ascertained from this information.

If you communicate directly with us via e-mail, complete one of our online forms, or use one of our other interactive tools, some of the information that you submit may be personal information (that is, information from which you can be identified, such as your full name, street address, e-mail address, phone number, and so on).

If you choose to provide your personal information to us, it may be used in order to:

  * contact you in respect of a query you made;
  * provide the services that you require and ensure our site is relevant to your needs;
  * deliver services such as email bulletins (if you have requested them);
  * answer your requests and queries;
  * research and develop our products and services;
  * gain an understanding of your needs in order to provide a better service;
  * promote and market our services;
  * protect our intellectual property and ownership rights, or
  * fulfil any legal requirements.

We may disclose your personal information to other organisations (for example our service providers) to enable us to provide the services you have requested, or as otherwise permitted by law.

## **Contacting us via email and our web forms**

When you contact The Web Showroom via email:

  * we will not disclose your email address without first obtaining your consent. You should keep in mind that the transmission of information over the Internet is not always completely secure or error-free. In particular, email sent to or from this website and information you enter into forms on our web-pages and send to us may not be secure. You should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email and web-forms.

## Search Engine Optimisation Privacy

We exercise a strict privacy policy for all clients whom elect to start a campaign centered on [search engine optimisation](http://www.thewebshowroom.com.au/seo/). Small businesses as well as enterprise companies often request that we sign an NDA to ensure The Web Showroom does not disclose to any 3rd parties that it is providing search engine optimisation services for the company’s website. This is not uncommon due to the competitive nature of the industries that our clients compete amongst. Please let a representative know if an NDA is required for any SEO services provided by The Web Showroom.

## **Our use of cookies**

When you visit our website, our server attaches a small data file called a "cookie" to your computer's memory.Cookies are pieces of information that may be transferred to your computer's memory when you visit a website for record keeping purposes. Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies. However, if you do not wish to receive any cookies you may set your Web browser to refuse cookies. We use cookies to provide us with aggregate (anonymous) information on how people use our website and to help us to know what they find interesting and useful about our website's design. We do not link this information back to your identity or other information that you have provided to us. We do not store any information that identifies you inside cookies.

## **Links to other websites**

This website may contain links or references to other websites. Our Website Privacy Statement does not extend beyond The Web Showroom website. When visiting other sites via a link on our website, you should familiarise yourself with the linked website's privacy statement.
